Guide to the Western Connecticut State University Photographs and Miscellanea RG 8
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series I: Photographs, 45605
  - Student Life, 45721
    - Fall Weekend/Homecoming, 45968
      - Princess candidates, parade, voting, bonfire[?] (Students: Nancy Marcinek, Patti Lutterman, Regina Rogala), ca.1970; 45974 (Box 14, Folder 18)
        Ten 5x7 b/w, and six 3.5 x 5 color
      - Skit/Song Competition, 1972-1978; 45973 (Box 14, Folder 19)
        23 5x7 b/w
      - Banner, football players, street scenes w/students, 1987; 45972 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Banner, street scenes w/students, 1989; 45971 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Student with sledge hammer/auto demolition ritual, ca.1990; 45970 (Box 14, Folder 22)
        One 3.5 x 5 color
      - Homecoming Parade and Events, 1965-1969; 45969 (Box 29, Folder 4)
        Color slides from Alumni Relations that appears to have been images assembled to show to reunion classes. Origninally, the slides were in a carousel with a projector.
      - Indoor/Outdoor Events, 1996-2000; 50063 (Box 10.1, Folder 7)
      - Homecoming; Candids (unlabeled), 1997; 50277 (Box 10.3, Folder 19)
      - Homecoming; Candids (unlabeled), 1999; 50278 (Box 10.3, Folder 20)
        17 4x6 color
    - Field Day, 45963
      - Students on field (from lantern slide), ca 1910-ca 1940, ca.1910-1930; 45967 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - Table tennis, ca.1940; 45966 (Box 14, Folder 23)
        Two 8x10, one 7x10 b/w
      - Badminton, 1940; 45965 (Box 14, Folder 24)
        Two 8x10
      - Archery, 1940; 45964 (Box 14, Folder 25)
        Two 8x10 and one 6x10 b/w
    - Field Trips, 45956
      - Geography class above Housatonic River, ca.1930; 45962 (Box 14, Folder 26)
        One 8x10 and one 3.5 x 6 b/w
      - Students entering wooded area (site unknown) ca 1930-ca 1940, 45961 (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - Natural Science class at Lake Candlewood w/Dr. Grant Finch, ca.1938-1939; 45960 (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - Natural Science class at Lake Candlewood, ca.1938-1939; 45959 (Box OS 3)
      - New York City and Metropolitan Museum of Art (outdoor), ca.1938-1939; 45958 (Box 14, Folder 29)
        Five 8x10 b/w
      - Washington, D. C., White House (outdoor), ca.1940; 45957 (Box 14, Folder 30)
        One 3x5 b/w
    - Formals/Dances, 45878
      - A Tea Dance (outdoor: women in long dresses carrying flowers) ca 1910-1994, ca.1910-1920; 45893 (Box OS 3)
        One 3.5 x 5 b/w (mounted) w/negative
      - B.O.G. sponsored 1950s dance, 1974-1975; 45882 (Box 15, Folder 48)
      - Dance: Harvest Ball (students dancing and group at table), ca.1940; 45892 (Box 15, Folder 38)
        One 7x7, one 6x7 b/w; one 5x7 b/w (mounted)
      - Prom "Maytime Magic" (students dancing and two men on glider), 1957; 45891 (Box 15, Folder 39)
        One 3x4 oval and one 3x3 b/w
      - Senior Prom Queen being crowned, 1958; 45890 (Box 15, Folder 40)
      - [Sweetheart Ball]? Two students holding flowers in front of valentines, ca.1960; 45889 (Box 15, Folder 41)
      - Junior Prom (candids of students and faculty), ca.1960; 45888 (Box 15, Folder 42)
        Six 5x7, one 4x5 and one 3x 4.5 b/w
      - ["Cider Glider" costumed dance]? Ralph Behrens and Don Scanlon in costume, Oct 1960; 45887 (Box 15, Folder 43)
      - Senior Prom "The Sugar Plum Ball" (students dancing), 1965; 45886 (Box 15, Folder 44)
        Seven 8x10 b/w
      - Senior Prom (couple dancing and group at table), 1968; 45884 (Box 15, Folder 46)
        Two 3.5 x 3.5 color
      - Junior Prom: Karen Burns and Michael Salvia, co-chairmen and students dancing), 1969; 45883 (Box 15, Folder 47)
      - Senior Semi-Formal (two students dancing), 1994; 45879 (Box 15, Folder 51)
      - Senior cocktail party, posed and candids and misc. candids, 2992; 50064 (Box 10.1, Folder 8)
        32 5x7 b/w w/negatives
      - Senior cocktail party, posed and candids and misc. candids, 1992; 50065 (Box 10.1, Folder 9)
        37 5x7 b/w w/negatives
      - Senior cocktail party, posed and candids and misc. candids, 1992; 50066 (Box 10.1, Folder 10)
        60 5x7 b/w w/negatives
      - Senior cocktail party, posed and candids and misc. candids, 1992; 50067 (Box 10.1, Folder 11)
        16 5x7 b/w w/negatives
      - Senior Dinner Dance, 1991; 50068 (Box 10.1, Folder 12)
        Ten 5x7 b/w
      - Senior Semi-Formal (posed and candids), 1992; 50069 (Box 10.1, Folder 13)
        33 5x7 b/w
      - Senior Semi-Formal (posed and candids), 1992; 50070 (Box 10.1, Folder 14)
      - Senior Semi-Formal (posed and candids), 1992; 50071 (Box 10.1, Folder 15)
        26 5x7 b/w
      - Winter Wonderland (posed & candids), 2992; 50072 (Box 10.1, Folder 16)
        15 5x7 b/w
      - Unknown (two students dancing in costume?), 1967; 45885 (Box 15, Folder 45)
      - Unknown, students dancing and around tables, 1977-1978; 45881 (Box 15, Folder 49)
      - Unknown, students dancing and around tables, 1978-1979; 45880 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Freshmen w/beanies, 45954
      - Orientation and candids (Sandra Wheadon, Jerri Fahy, Pam Isbill, Jo Adamo, Charlie Allen, Beth Morgan), ca.1950-1960; 45955 (Box 14, Folder 31)
        17 various sizes (8x10 to 3.5 x 3.5 b/w) w/negatives
    - Halloween, 45948
      - Students in costume (1974 yearbook), 1973-1978, 45953 (Box 14, Folder 32)
      - Three students dressed in "Wizard of Oz" costumes (1975 yearbook), 1974; 45952 (Box 14, Folder 33)
      - Students in costume (1976 yearbook), 1975; 45951 (Box 14, Folder 34)
      - Students in costume (1978 yearbook), 1977; 45950 (Box 14, Folder 35)
        18 5x7 b/w
      - Students in costume (1979 yearbook), 1978; 45949 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Initiation Week, 45946
      - Students dressed in cook's hats and aprons (Students:Carmella Vadola, Nancy Clark, Louise Brunberg, Gloria Lawson, Rosebell Wells, Marilyn Ross, Barbara Bader, Ruth Hermanschorffer, Mary Carrio, Eunice Cashman, Beverly Sutton, Candy Sigritta), 1946; 45947 (Box 14, Folder 37)
        Three 2.5 x 3.5 b/w
    - Job Fairs, 45944
      - Students w/prospective employers, ca.1970-1990; 45945 (Box 14, Folder 38)
        One 5x7 b/w; two 4x6 color
    - Las Vegas Night, 45941
      - Students and Dean Lafond, ca 1970-ca 1990, 1975; 45943 (Box 14, Folder 39)
      - Students around gaming tables and croupiers, ca.1977-1990; 45942 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Latin American Pageant, 45939
      - Students in Latin American costume, 1944, 45940 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Music Performing Groups, 45916
      - A Cappella Choir, indoor group, 1938-ca 1970, 1938-1941; 45938 (Box 15, Folder 1)
        Three 8x10 and one 5x10 b/w
      - Band, students in classroom, 1959-1960; 45937 (Box 15, Folder 2)
        Two 8x10, three 5x7 one 5x7 (mounted) and one 4x5 b/w
      - Band, football games and graduation (outdoor), ca.1960-1970; 45936 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Band (indoor, performance unknown), ca.1960; 45935 (Box 15, Folder 4)
        Two 5x7 and one 3.5 x 3.5, one 2.5 x 3 b/w
      - Brass ensemble, Daniel D'Addio conducting, ca.1990; 45934 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Choir (outdoor), 1947-1948; 45933 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Chorus (outdoor), 1948-1949; 45932 (Box OS 3)
      - Chorus (classroom and unknown event), ca.1950-1960; 45931 (Box 15, Folder 7)
        One 8x10, one 5x7, and one 3.5 x 3.5 b/w
      - Chorus (Christmas party), 1967; 45930 (Box 15, Folder 8)
        Two 3.5 x 3.5 and two 3.5 x 5 b/w
      - Chorus, Women's (indoor around piano), 1959-1960; 45929 (Box 15, Folder 9)
        One 8x9 b/w (mounted)
      - Chorus, Women's (Christmas carolers?), ca.1960; 45928 (Box 15, Folder 10)
        One 5x7
      - Danbury Choral Society "Messiah" includes DTSC students Terry Scott, Anthony Sagnello and Doris Videtto, Dec 1948; 45927 (Box OS 3)
      - Danbury Choral Society "Messiah" includes DTSC students Terry Scott, Anthony Sagnello and Doris Videtto, Dec 1948; 45926 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Glee Club "Feast of the Little Lanterns", Dec 1934; 45925 (Box 15, Folder 12)
        One 5x9 b/w
      - Jazz concert (outdoor), ca.1965; 45924 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Orchestra (indoor on stage), 1947-1948; 45923 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Orchestra (indoor on stage), 1955-1956; 45922 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Orchestra (classroom), ca.1960; 45921 (Box 15, Folder 16)
        One 8x10 b/w and one 6x9 b/w (mounted)
      - Orchestra (performance unknown), ca.1960; 45920 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Percussion Ensemble, Dave Smith conductor, ca.1970; 45919 (Box 15, Folder 18)
        Two 5x7 and one 4x5 b/w (w/negatives)
      - Unknown recital with students A.Bocclino, K.Hemmot, P.Laska, E.Benoit, B.Beninco, R.Oligino, L.Lewis, R.Miller), ca.1960; 45918 (Box 15, Folder 19)
        One 3.5 x 4 b/w
      - Wesconn Singers with James Furman, 1969; 45917 (Box 15, Folder 20)
        One 5.5 x 5.5 and one 8x10
      - Holiday Concert, 1998; 50282 (Box 10.3, Folder 18)
      - Concert choir (indoor), 2000; 50287 (Box 10.3, Folder 27)
      - Groups (unlabeled), ca.2000; 50288 (Box 10.3, Folder 28)
        12 4x6 and one 3.5x5 color
    - Music Students, 45912
      - Senior Recital: Robert M. Pettinicchi with snare drum performing with Mattatuck Drum Band of Waterbury, Mar 1964; 45915 (Box 15, Folder 21)
        One 7x9 b/w
      - Event unknown: Marlene Dunleavy, James Papp, Vincent Biscoglio, Donald Smith, Eloise Kilcoyne, Edith James, ca.1960; 45914 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      - Events unknown; choral and instrumental, ca.1968-1980; 45913 (Box 15, Folder 23)
        Two 8x10 and 17 5x7, two 4x6, and one 4x4 b/w
    - Music Students with faculty, 45906
      - Keyboard Harmony Class, Miss Clark, ca 1960-ca 1990, 45911 (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - James Furman directing school choir, ca.1960; 45910 (Box 15, Folder 25)
        One 8x10
      - James Furman with four choir members, 1968-1969; 45909 (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - Marceau Meyers with students Marge Finck, Louis Manoni, and Carol Raymond, ca.1960; 45908 (Box 15, Folder 27)
        One 8x10 and two 5x7 b/w
      - Howard Tuvelle with students Raymond J. Small and Joseph Unfried, winners of Broacast Music, Inc.'s 18th University Musical Show Competition, ca.1990; 45907 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Nuro Research Trip, 45904
      - Dr. Dawson: Students Jennifer Howald and Jose Herrero outside observatory, w/ 31 inch telescope and photometer, data center, processing CCD images at Sun workstation. Also at Walnut Canyon, Grand Canyon and rim of Meteor Crater., Nov 1992; 45905 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Protests/Demonstrations, 45896
      - Peace group outside of Higgins Hall, 1967-1979, 1967-1968; 45903 (Box 15, Folder 30)
      - Placards against VietNam war and discussion group, 1969-1970; 45902 (Box 15, Folder 31)
      - Students protest tuition increases, 1973-1974; 45901 (Box 15, Folder 32)
      - AFT members and students protesting state budget cuts, 1973-1974; 45900 (Box 15, Folder 33)
        Seven 5x7 and one 4x6 b/w
      - Students for [Governor] Ella Grasso, 1974; 45899 (Box 15, Folder 34)
      - Miscellaneous, 1977-1978; 45898 (Box 15, Folder 35)
      - Mock funeral for higher education (Westside campus site), 1979; 45897 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Registration/Orientation, 45894
      - Candids of students and faculty (includes freshmen wearing beanies), ca.1960; 45895 (Box 15, Folder 37)
        One 8x10, 10 5x7, one 3.5 x 5, and two 3.5 x 3.5 b/w
      - Orientation Leaders, 2000; 50289 (Box 10.3, Folder 29)
        Three 4x6 color Public Relations Society
    - Scrapbook, 45870
      - Scrapbook assembled by a member of the Danbury Normal School class of 1918. Scrapbook may have belonged to an M. Atkins., 2003; 45877
        Scanned in 2003, original not held by the WCSU Archives.
      - [Jessie C. Tripp?] DNS Senior A Division Field Trip; Rural Club; Trip to Washington; Field Day; DNS Class Day (students and faculty identified) 1925-1949, 1925-1926; 45876 (Box 16, Folder 1)
        24 Various sizes (2x3 to 3.5 x 6) b/w
      - [Mrs. Bruce E. Haeger?] DTC Do-Day, Interim Trip, Rye Beach, Cupid's Fancy Semi Formal, and candids], 1948-1951; 45875 (Box 16, Folder 2 and 3)
        81 various sizes (4x5 to 5x6) b/w
      - [Unknown] Acc.2002.6 Students in front of Fairfield Hall (Barbara Bader, Mary Jaser, Nila Koulbanis, Dick Mansfield), 1935-1949; 45874 (Box 16, Folder 3a)
        One 3x 4.5 and six 2.5 x 3.5 b/w
      - [Louise Johnson?] Acc.2002.6 Students (Art Coladarci, Anne Marie Dyer, Carmella? Cippola, Danny Skandera, Ray Keane, Frieda Korntheuer, Cora Russell), 1937-1939; 45873 (Box 16, Folder 3b)
        Three 2.5 x 3.5, one 2.5 x 4.5 b/w
      - [Unknown] Acc.2002.7 Members of Junior D. Division and Council, 1929; 45872 (Box 16, Folder 3c)
        Two 2.5 x 3.5 b/w
      - [Unknown] Dorm Women, Field Day, Maypole, 1926; 45871 (Box 16, Folder 3)
        Five 2.5 x 3.5 b/w
    - Spring Weekend, 45845
      - Skit (unknown with Anthony Dilluvio), 1965-1979, 45869 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - King & Queen (Bill Gannon and Marge Byiteck and candids of students), 1965; 45868 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Danbury Town Park Picnic, 1966; 45867 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Floats ("New York World's Fair" and "There is Peace and Unity"), 1966; 45866 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Sing winners (Juniors "The Music Man"), 1967; 45865 (Box 16, Folder 8)
        One 3x6 b/w
      - Skits (freshmen and sophomore classes), 1967; 45864 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Jane Wilhousky leads combined chorus, 1967; 45863 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - King & Queen (Gary Field & Maggie Marfiak), 1968; 45862 (Box 16, Folder 11)
        One 3.5 x 5 b/w w/negatives
      - Skit/Sing Competition, 1968; 45861 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Floats and parade, 1969; 45860 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - King and Queen (Richard Theriault and Donna Strobino), 1969; 45859 (Box 16, Folder 14)
        Five 4x5 b/w (Polaroid)
      - Skit/Sing competition, 1969; 45858 (Box 16, Folder 15)
        Eight 4x5 b/w and three 5x7 b/w
      - Skit/Sing competition, 1973; 45857 (Box 16, Folder 16)
        13 - 5x7 b/w
      - Skit/Sing competition, 1974; 45856 (Box 16, Folder 17)
        14 various sizes (2x2.5 - 3 x 3.5 to 5x7) b/w and color
      - Lake Kenosia Clambake (candids of students), 1974; 45855 (Box 16, Folder 18)
        One 3.5 x 5 and one 3x4 color
      - Skit/Sing competition, 1974; 45854 (Box OS 3)
        One 4x5 color (mounted)
      - Skit/Sing competition, 1976; 45853 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Skit/Sing competition, 1977; 45852 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Lake Kenosia Clambake (candids of students), 1977; 45851 (Box 16, Folder 21)
        Three 5x7 b/w; four 3.5 x 5 color
      - Skit/Sing competition, Winners of Sing, Class of 1979, 1978; 45850 (Box 16, Folder 22)
      - Lake Kenosia Clam Bake (candids of students), 1978; 45849 (Box 16, Folder 23)
        39 5x7 b/w
      - Lake Kenosia Clam Bake (candids of students), 1978; 45848 (Box 16, Folder 24)
      - Skit/Sing competition, 1979; 45847 (Box 16, Folder 25)
        31 5x7 b/w
      - Lake Kenosia Clam Bake (candids of students), 1979; 45846 (Box 16, Folder 26)
        60 5x7 b/w
      - Senior Sing Contest (Class of 1965, Jack Sikora), 50075 (Box 30, Folder *)
        One reel to reel 1/4" magnetic tape
    - Student Teaching, 45831
      - Laboratory Student Work Project, 1910-1970, 45844 (Box 17, Folder 1)
        Two 3.5 x 5.5 b/w
      - Locust Avenue Laboratory students (outdoor), 1910; 45843 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Miry Brook Laboratory School students (outdoor), 1912; 45842 (Box 17, Folder 3)
        Two 5x8 b/w
      - Laboratory School (unknown) students (indoor and outdoor), ca.1915; 45841 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Kindergarten Class in DNS (indoor and outdoor), ca.1915; 45840 (Box 17, Folder 5)
        Three 3.5 x 5.5 b/w
      - Kindergarten Class "En Voyage" ca 1930, 45839 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Laboratory school classroom unknown, 1931; 45838 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Laboratory school classroom unknown, 1939; 45837 (Box 17, Folder 8)
        Ten 8x10 b/w
      - Laboratory school classroom unknown, ca.1940; 45836 (Box 17, Folder 9)
        Six 8x10, one 5x7 and one 3.5 x 5 b/w
      - Laboratory school classroom unknown, ca.1950-1960; 45835 (Box 17, Folder 10)
        33 Various sizes (8x10 - 2.5 x 4 b/w)
      - Locust Avenue T.V. Program, 1969; 45834 (Box 17, Folder 11)
        Five 3.5 x 3.5 b/w and negatives
      - Dr. Isham's art exhibit, 1969; 45833 (Box 17, Folder 12)
        Eight 3.5 x 3.5 b/w and negatives
      - Dr. Halb's Workshop, 1970; 45832 (Box 17, Folder 13)
        Ten 3.5 x 3.5 b/w and contact sheet w/negatives
    - Theatrical Productions, 45804
      - A Funny Thing Happened On the Way to the Forum 1940-ca 1980, Mar 1974; 45830 (Box 17, Folder 14)
        Two 5x7 and one 4x6 blakc and white
      - Blithe Spirit (Cast:, Nov 1970; 45829 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Claudia (Cast: Dorothy Curtiss, Thomas McDonough, Jean Albright, Bertha Feldbin, Wendell Clark, Floriene Abrahams, Sally Guss, Warren Jagush), 1947-1948; 45828 (Box 17, Folder 16)
        One 4.5 x 6 b/w
      - Death Takes a Holiday (Cast: T.Warner, D.Clarke, M.Williamson, R.Stratton, M.Burke, J.Browne, L.Kauffman, J.Zucca, H.Marsh, R.Braibanti, B.McAllister, C.White, R.Schappals), Nov 1940; 45827 (Box 17, Folder 17)
        One 7x10 b/w
      - Enemy of the People (Cast:L.Barni, P.Zimmerman, T.Dillon, D.Chedd, F.Gentile, R.Parks, A.Ryerson), Nov 1970; 45826 (Box 17, Folder 18)
        11 3.5 x 3.5 b/w w/negatives
      - Fiddler on the Roof, 1984; 45825 (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - The Flies (Cast: Joseph Sabol, Brenda Ganz), Nov 1959; 45824 (Box 17, Folder 20)
        Two 8x10 and one 4x5 b/w w/negative
      - Grease, Nov 1993; 45823 (Box 17, Folder 21)
        Three 4x6 b/w
      - Invitation to a March Cast rehearsal with Dr. Alfred Golding (Cast: R.Winans, J.Gardiner, A.Desdreneaux, R.Kuba, J.Photis, B.Blanchard, R.Gallagher), undated; 45822 (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - Iolanthe (Cast: Mort Johnson, James Murry Burke, Truman A. Warner), Apr 1964; 45821 (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - Iolanthe [donated by Mort Johnson, class of 1942], May 1940; 45820 (Box 17, Folder 24)
        Seven 3 x 4.5 b/w
      - Kismit cast members party at Oasis, Apr 1962; 45819 (Box 17, Folder 25)
        One 4x5 b/w w/negatives
      - Many Moons (Faculty with stage props: Richard H. Moryl and Alfred S. Golding), ca.1950; 45818 (Box 17, Folder 26)
        One 5x6 b/w
      - The Night of January 16 (Cast: V.Kaspar, R.Sidney, R.Hayman, W.Clark, L.Lawson, T.Scott, J. Carr, A. Sagnella, H.Russel, V.Mikulics, D.Gemza, J.Gabriele, F.DiNapioli, J.Morrison, E.Stephany, M.Carrio, C. Rotello, G.deVriendt, A.Ciccaroni), Mar 1949; 45817 (Box 17, Folder 27)
      - Oh, What a Lovely War, 1982; 45816 (Box 17, Folder 28)
      - Patience, Apr 1942; 45815 (Box 17, Folder 29a)
        Eight 8x10 b/w
      - Pippin, ca.1970-1980; 45814 (Box 17, Folder 29b)
      - [Revolutionary Play]?, Dec 1932; 45813 (Box 17, Folder 30)
      - Romeo and Juliet (All male cast: Students: V.DeFlumer, N.Kuback, R.Pascellralli, P.Pecknic, C.Mortaro, H. White, J.Allo, N.McColgan, V.Stranneri, E.McGivern, J.Mauro, T. Costello, L.Lubus, E.Kramer, P.Petnik; Faculty: John Murphy, Carl Pettersch, F.Burton Cook, Chester Floyd), 1949; 45812 (Box 17, Folder 31)
        12 4x5 b/w
      - Scopino (Cast: Mike Patterson, Todd Judson, John Farias, Vincent Roco, Jennifer Anderson, Rema Sayegh, Rick Ercole, Robert Green, Joe Loffredo, Kristin Eifert), Mar 1994; 45811 (Box 17, Folder 32)
        One 5x7 and two 4x6 b/w
      - Stop the World, I Want to Get Off (Cast: Donna Pullen, Andrea Martin, Lauren Cook, Laurie Coppa, Karin NeJame, Stephen Daley), ca.1970; 45810 (Box 17, Folder 33)
      - You Can't Take It With You (Cast: H.Leary, M.Blake, K.Tyler, R.Keane, M.Barron, C.White, T.Shanon, C.Swenson, B.Sullivan, M.Burke, J.Grentzner, A.Coladarci, E.Stokes, A.Rosen, M.Keler, H.Marsh, W.Laws, A.Strand), Jan 1940; 45809 (Box 17, Folder 34)
      - Unknown (man on sitting on bench with girl holding umbrella), ca.1967; 45808 (Box 17, Folder 35)
      - Unknown (Dr. Alfred Golding coaching students), 1958-1959; 45807 (Box 17, Folder 36)
        Three 4x5 b/w w/negatives
      - Unknown (Richard Reimold with student), ca.1980; 45806 (Box 17, Folder 37)
      - Unknown, ca.1990; 45805 (Box 17, Folder 38)
        45 various sizes (8x10 - 3.5 x 4 b/w and color) and three 4x5 b/w negatives
      - Theatrical and art show (unknown), 1992; 50062 (Box 10.1, Folder 6)
        14 3.5x5 color w/negative
      - Aurora Repertory Theatre, 1995 (Box 10.4, Folder 6.1)
        2, 8 x 10" black and white prints with descriptive materials.
      - A Funny Thing Happened On theWay to the Forum (Cast members inlcude Ginny and Roy Young), 2000; 50294 (Box 10.4, Folder 8)
      - Amahl and the Night Visitors, 2000; 50295 (Box 10.4, Folder 9)
      - Amahl and the Night Visitors, ca.2000; 50296 (Box 10.4, Folder 10)
      - Antigone, ca.2000; 50297 (Box 10.4, Folder 11)
      - The Cherry Orchard (New York City show) cast members (unlabeled), 2002; 50298 (Box 10.4, Folder 12)
      - Forces of Dance, ca.2000; 50299 (Box 10.4, Folder 13)
      - Funny Girl (Dinner Theater), 1999; 50300 (Box 10.4, Folder 14)
      - Macbeth, 2000; 50301 (Box 10.4, Folder 15)
        Three 3.5x5 color
      - Suburbia, 2000; 50302 (Box 10.4, Folder 16)
    - WestConn Christian Ministry, 45802
      - Building project, Catemaco, Mexico, 1997; 45803 (Box 17, Folder 39)
        One 4x10 and two 4x6 color
    - Winter Weekend, 45797
      - Location unknown (Students by fireplace, on bunkbeds, having dinner and group ski lesson) 1957-1958, 45801 (Box 17, Folder 40)
        One 8x10 mounted; one 7x8 (mounted) and 6 varyious sizes (.75 x 2.5 to 2x3 b/w) w/negatives
      - Formal dance (group at table), 1969; 45800 (Box 17, Folder 41)
      - Competitive events: art, music, theatre and poetry readings, 1973; 45799 (Box 17, Folder 42)
      - 1950s dance, 1974; 45798 (Box 17, Folder 43)
      - Winter Warm Up (includes Mayor Eriquez and Newman Club), ca.2000; 50312 (Box 10.4, Folder 19)
    - WXCI 91.7 FM, 45795
      - Campus Radio Station, ca.1940-1970; 45796 (Box 17, Folder 44)
        14 various sizes (8x10 - 3.5x5 b/w) w/negatives
      - Group and Individuals, Posed (unlabeled), ca.2000; 50303 (Box 10.4, Folder 21)
        Four 4x6 b/w
    - WICC-TV, Ch.43, 45793
      - Three students(?) with television camera, ca.1950; 45794 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Yearbook, 45763
      - Groups and portrait (unlabeled), ca.1930-1990; 45792 (Box 18, Folder 1)
        Four various sizes (2.5 x 3.5 to 3.5 x 6) b/w
      - Groups (identified), ca.1930; 45791 (Box 18, Folder 2)
        One 2.5x3.5 and one 3x5 b/w
      - Groups (unlabeled), ca.1940; 45790 (Box 18, Folder 3)
        Four various sizes (3.5x5.5 to 5x7) b/w
      - Fairfield Hall Public Room w/students, editorial board 1948 Yearbook, ca.1940; 45789 (Box OS 3)
      - Candids, individuals and groups (includes Faculty Fling 1957), ca.1950; 45788 (Box 18, Folder 4)
        20 various sizes (5x7 to 2x2) b/w
      - Portraits (identified), ca.1950; 45787 (Box 18, Folder 5)
        58 2.5 x 3 b/w
      - Group of men (unlabled), ca.1950-1960; 45786 (Box OS 3)
        One 10x10 b/w
      - Groups (unlabeled), ca.1960; 45785 (Box 19, Folder 1)
        Four 8x10, two 5x7, and one 7x8 b/w
      - Groups (unlabeled), ca.1960; 45784 (Box 18, Folder 6)
        18 various sizes b/w (2x2 to 4x5) and one 3.5x3.5 color
      - Portraits (identified), ca.1960; 45783 (Box 18, Folder 7)
        25 various sizes (2.5 x 3 and 5x7) b/w
      - Portraits (unlabeled), ca.1960; 45782 (Box 18, Folder 8)
        10 various sizes (2.5 x 5x7) b/w
      - Groups (unlabeled), ca.1960; 45781 (Box 18, Folder 9)
        Seven 5x7 and one 4x5 b/w
      - Candids (unlabeled), ca.1960; 45780 (Box 18, Folder 10)